futurestradingcoach.com 2014-02-09

# The Futures Trading Coach Privacy Policy

**What information does Futures Trading Coach.com collect from  our users and how do we collect it?**

Futures Trading Coach.com only contacts individuals who specifically request that we do so or in the event that they have signed up to receive our free newsletters or have made a purchase from our website.

Futures Trading Coach.com collects personally identifying information from our users during online registration and online purchasing.

Generally, this information includes name and e-mail address for registration to receive our free newsletters and name, postal address, and credit card information when purchasing our products.

All of this information is provided to us by you.

**How do we use this information?**

This information is used for internal marketing purposes only. Futures Trading Coach.com does not sell, exchange, or release your personal information (name, e-mail address, mailing address, credit data, etc.)

Your information is not shared with anyone apart from with our affiliated merchant partners.

**What are cookies and how do we use them?**

Cookies help track a person's "session" while online. By showing how and when our visitors use this Site, this information can help us to continue to improve our Site.

We will only use cookies to view information on your hard drive that was put there by a cookie from this Site.

The use of cookies is an industry standard and many web sites use them. Cookies are stored on your computer and not on this Site.

If you do not wish to receive cookies, or want to be notified of when they are placed, you may set your web browser to do so, if your browser so permits.

**How do we store your information?**

Your information is stored at the list server that delivers Futures Trading Coach.com's courses and newsletters.

Your information can only be accessed by those who help manage those lists in order to deliver e-mail to those who would like to receive Local Web Solution's newsletters. 

All of the newsletters that are sent to you by Futures Trading Coach.com include an unsubscribe link in them. You can remove yourself at any time from our newsletters by clicking on the unsubscribe link.

You can also contact us [here](http://www.futurestradingcoach.com/futures-trading-contact.html) to change your information at any time.

**Children’s Privacy**

We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13. If we learn that we have personal information on a child under the age of 13, we will delete that information from our systems. 

Futures Trading Coach.com encourages parents to go online with their kids. Here are a few tips to help make a child's online experience safer:

Teach kids never to give personal information, unless supervised by a parent or responsible adult. Includes name, address, phone, school, etc. 

Know the sites your kids are visiting and which sites are appropriate. 

Look for Web site privacy policies. Know how your child's information is treated. 

[Check out the FTC's site here](http://www.ftc.gov/bcp/conline/edcams/kidzprivacy/index.html) for more tips on protecting children's privacy online. 

**Cookie Opt-Out**

**Disclaimer**

This policy may be changed at any time at Futures Trading Coach.com's discretion. If we should update this policy, we will post the updates to this page on our Website. This policy was revised November 7, 2006. 

If you have any questions or concerns regarding our privacy policy please direct them [here](http://www.futurestradingcoach.com/futures-trading-contact.html)

You may also contact us by mail at: 

**Futures Trading Coach**

**144 Concord Place  
King of Prussia  
PA 19406**

**U.S. Government Required Disclaimer -** Commodity Futures Trading Commission Futures and Options trading has large potential rewards, but also large potential risk. You must be aware of the risks and be willing to accept them in order to invest in the futures and options markets. Don't trade with money you can't afford to lose. This is neither a solicitation nor an offer to Buy/Sell futures or options. No representation is being made that any account will or is likely to achieve profits or losses similar to those discussed on this web site. The past performance of any trading system or methodology is not necessarily indicative of future results. 

**CFTC RULE 4.41 -** HYPOTHETICAL OR SIMULATED PERFORMANCE RESULTS HAVE CERTAIN LIMITATIONS. UNLIKE AN ACTUAL PERFORMANCE RECORD, SIMULATED RESULTS DO NOT REPRESENT ACTUAL TRADING. ALSO, SINCE THE TRADES HAVE NOT BEEN EXECUTED, THE RESULTS MAY HAVE UNDER-OR-OVER COMPENSATED FOR THE IMPACT, IF ANY, OF CERTAIN MARKET FACTORS, SUCH AS LACK OF LIQUIDITY. SIMULATED TRADING PROGRAMS IN GENERAL ARE ALSO SUBJECT TO THE FACT THAT THEY ARE DESIGNED WITH THE BENEFIT OF HINDSIGHT. NO REPRESENTATION IS BEING MADE THAT ANY ACCOUNT WILL OR IS LIKELY TO ACHIEVE PROFIT OR LOSSES SIMILAR TO THOSE SHOWN.
